

Mariana Inácio

\(+351 910 361 111

Mariana Inácio

Mariana Inácio

Be Mariana Inácio

PROFILE

Name

Mariana de Carvalho Pereira Inácio

Birthday

1.08.1995

Nationality

Portuguese

Gender

Female

I am a 23 year old UX designer. I am very creative and always try to approach a problem from every angle, so that I can find the best solution. I am detail oriented, as I believe that it can make or break the experience.

I have strong work ethics and strive to keep learning, while keeping an open mind to different points of view.

Portfolio

EDUCATION

WEB DESIGN

ETIC Lisboa (October 2018 - June 2019)

POSTGRADUATE CERTIFICATE WITH MERIT IN DIGITAL DESIGN

DeMonfort University, Leicester, United Kingdom (March 2018)

BA MULTIMEDIA ART INTERACTIVE ENVIRONMENTS

Faculdade de Belas-Artes da Universidade de Lisboa, Portugal (June 2017)

LANGUAGES

Portuguese (native speaker) English (C1)

EXPERIENCE

UX/UI DESIGNER

Iron Portugal

(March 2019 - May 2019)

Content Creation:

Design Research:

Motion Graphics;

UX/UI Design (Wireframming,

low and high fedelity

Prototypes)

JUNIOR DESIGNER

Iron Portugal

(September 2018 - February 2019)

Content creation;

Content translation (PT/EN)

Coordenation between design

and developper teams;

Design Reseach;

Motion Graphics;

Quality Assurance;

UX/UI Design (Wireframming,

low and high fedelity

Prototypes)

MARKETING INTERNSHIP

NOESIS Portugal

(June 2014 - September 2014)

Event Planing;

Reports, Leaflets and

Newsletters Layouts;

Newsletters Management;

Social Media Mananagement.

HARD SKILLS

Adobe Creative Suite

After Effects

Illustrator

Indesign

Photoshop

Premiere

XD

HTML/CSS

JavaScript

SOFT SKILLS

Communication

Creativity

Leadership

Problem Solving

Responsability

Teamwork

Time Management

Work Ethics

INTERESTS

Art History

Coding

Gender Studies

Interactive Art

Literature

Motion Graphics

Politics

UX/UI